我没抽到你 Peralta
I don't have you, Peralta.
我不光知道你抽到的是我
Not only do I know that you do indeed have me,
我还知道你们都抽着谁了
but I also know who everyone else has.
总监: 八圈
不可能
That's not possible.
对于你这样的平凡人来说也许不可能 Jeffords
Perhaps not for an ordinary man such as yourself, Jeffords.
但是对于我这么聪明的人
But for the brilliant mind of
Jacob Sherlock Peralta警探
Detective Jacob Sherlock Peralta...
我已经正式改了名字
I legally changed my name...
这不过是很简单的
it's quite simply...
基本演绎法
elementary.
你看 Amy做了一个表情
For, you see, Amy made a face
我只在我俩卧室里见过的那种
I only recognized from our bedroom,
说明她抽到了Holt警监
which means that she has Captain Holt.
Charles抽到了Terry 他的眼睛不停地看向他
Charles has Terry. His eyes keep shifting over to him.
不 我没看
No, I don't.
Terry看起来被恶心着了
Terry looked disgusted,
那就说明他抽到了Hitchcock
which means he has Hitchcock.
Rosa没抽 也没把自己的名字放进去
Rosa didn't draw a name, nor did she put one in.
- 她并不想参与  - 从来没想过
- She doesn't wanna participate. - Never do.
默读名字的时候Hitchcock动了嘴唇
Hitchcock moves his mouth when he reads